worldatlas.com 2019-10-10

# Worldatlas.com and Graphic Maps Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 10, 2018. 

##  Legal ownership 

WorldAtlas.com (the “Website”) is owned and operated by Reunion Technology Inc (“us” or “we”), a corporation incorporated under the laws of Canada, having its head office at 7405 Transcanada Highway, Suite 100, Saint Laurent, Quebec H4T 1Z2. 

##  Personal Data Collected 

When you visit our Website, we collect certain information related to your device, such as your IP address, what pages you visit on our Website, whether you were referred to by another website, and at what time you accessed our Website. We do not collect any other type of personal data. If you are accessing our website through a social media account, please refer to the social media provider’s privacy policy for information regarding their data collection. 

##  Log Files 

Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/timestamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

##  Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We only use cookies to track progression on quizzes that are posted on our website. This is only a functional cookie and no personal data is collected. However, some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. 

##  Links 

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site. 

##  Advertisers 

We use third-party advertising companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect usage and demographic data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, we do not have access to this information. We work with ad companies such as Google Adsense. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We have reviewed all of our advertising partners’ policies to ensure that they comply with all applicable data privacy laws and recommended data security practices. 

##  Purpose of Data Collection 

We use the information we collect in order to: \- Administer our Website, including troubleshooting, and statistical or data analysis; \- To improve our Website and enhancing user experience by ensuring you have access to personalized content in line with your interests; \- Analyze user use and optimize our services. \- To ensure that our Website remains secure and is not subject to any hacking or fraud. 

##  Data shared with third parties 

We do not sell or rent your data to third parties. However, our partners, including ad partners, may collect data in relation to your Website using as disclosed below. Please see our “advertisers” section above for details. 

##  How your Data is Stored 

All data collected through our Website is stored on servers located in the United States. Our servers are certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield. IP address and user agent string data from all visitors is stored in rotating log files on Amazon servers for up to 7 days. All of our employees, agents and partners are committed to keeping your data confidential. 

We have reviewed our partners privacy policies to ensure that they comply with similar policies in order to ensure your data security. 

##  Consent under applicable laws 

If you are based in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), a consent window will appear when accessing this website. If you have clicked “yes”, your consent will be stored on our servers for six (6) months and your data will be processed as disclosed in this privacy policy. After six months, you will be asked to provide consent again. You can withdraw consent at any time. Withdrawing consent may impede your ability to access certain services and will not allow us to provide the personalized Website experience. 

##  Data Security 

Our servers comply with ISO 27018, a code of practice that focuses on protection of personal data in the cloud. We comply with all reasonable precautions in order to ensure your data’s safety. 

In the event that we become aware of any data security breach, alteration, unauthorized access or disclosure of any personal data, we will take all reasonable precautions to protect your data and will notify you as required by all applicable laws. 

##  Accessing, Amending and Deleting your data 

You have the right to request information regarding the data we have on file for you, to request correction and/or deletions of your personal information. Please contact us at data@valnetinc.com or at the postal address listed above. 

##  Age 

This Website does not target people below the age of 13. By visiting this Website. You hereby warrant that you are 13 years of age or older or are visiting the Website under parental supervision. 

##  Legal Disclaimer 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of our sites. 

##  Notification of Changes 

Whenever we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy page, and other places we deem appropriate, so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

##  Contact Information 

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at data@worldatlas.com. 

## Trending on WorldAtlas

This page was last updated on **May 15, 2018**.
